dominos.com.my 2010-05-11

# Domino's Pizza Malaysia - Privacy

Domino's Pizza Malaysia Pte Ltd ("Domino's") acknowledges and respects the privacy of individuals. This policy covers the personal information that Domino's and its franchisees hold and sets out the way in which Domino's and its franchisees will use, manage and protect your personal information when you visit any of our websites, or place an order with one of our stores.

Domino's may revise this policy from time to time whenever necessary so check this website regularly to stay informed of any updates. This policy is effective as from December 2009.

How Do We Collect Information?

Domino's may collect personal information from you including your first and last name, address, telephone and mobile number(s), email address, credit card details and any other information, when you knowingly provide us with this information. This will generally occur when you either:

visit our web sites;  
enter into a competition or promotion;  
participate in a survey;  
subscribe to our mailing list;  
register as an emember;  
apply for a job;  
submit website feedback; or  
place a pizza order via store or via our internet system.

Where Domino's collects personal information about you from someone else, Domino's will take reasonable steps to advise you.

How Do We Use Information?

Domino's may use the personal information that you submit to store and process that information in order to provide goods and services. Generally, we may use your personal information in the ways in which you would expect, including but not limited, to any of the following purposes:

to process any job application you may submit;  
to provide you with any company information you may request;  
to process any online ordering;  
to determine the number of visitors to our websites and conduct reviews of our sites;  
to fulfil prizes, awards and purchases;  
to respond to specific requests from visitors;  
to keep you informed about any changes to our websites;  
to conduct marketing research; and  
to now and again send you offers or information on products or services that we consider will be of interest to you.

Further information on how we use your personal information when using our Internet ordering system.

When using the Domino's Pizza internet ordering system additional information is collected when you order a pizza online. This information assists in the delivery to your door and to verify your credit card payment. The internet order system also stores information about your order to help you remember and re-order the same menu in future. 

ECoupons

Domino’s ecoupon to be redeemed via Domino's Pizza Internet order system. Go to the 'Online Order' page, select the 'Online e-Coupon' button, and select your e-coupon. This information is then processed by Domino's Pizza in order to verify and provide your discount.

Third Party Disclosure

Domino's may share statistics and personal information with companies that are related to Domino's including our international branches.

Personal information that you submit to Domino's may be disclosed to a third party:

Such as our suppliers who are employed to provide some of our services such as mailing houses;  
to meet the purpose for which it was submitted;  
if you have provided your express consent to share the information;  
if Domino's are required or authorised by law to disclose the information;  
if your personal information is collected in connection with a joint promoter, to that joint promoter for marketing and research purposes;  
if Domino's feel you might like to know about a third party's goods and services we may supply that personal information to that third party. (We know that many of our customers enjoy receiving these excellent offers); or  
if you place an order via our internet order system, your details will be passed on to Verisign, who receive your credit card details for internet order payment. Verisign is a secure internet payment gateway that secures your credit card number during transmission. See: www.verisign.com for further details.

Access, Accuracy and Security

Domino's will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information collected is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

You can access and request correction of any personal information concerning you at any time. You may also request that your personal information be deleted at any time. Any such requests should be made directly by contacting us (see "Contact Us" section below).

Domino's will take reasonable steps to protect personal information from misuse, loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.  

Sensitive Information

Domino's will not collect, use or disclose sensitive information (such as information about racial or ethnic origins or political or religious beliefs) except with your specific consent or in the circumstances permitted in the Malaysian privacy laws or any other related laws in Malaysia.  

Clickstream Data

Each time you visit the Domino's site our server collects some anonymous information, known as click-stream data, including the type of browser and system you are using; the address of the site you have come from and move to after your visit; the date and time of your visit; and your server's IP address.

Domino's may collect this information for statistical purposes to find out how the websites is used and navigated, including the number of hits, the frequency and duration of visits, most popular session times. Domino's may use this information to evaluate and improve the Domino's websites.
